<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<post>
		<ID>223</ID>
		<Title>All the Rage Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[A delightful, multi-colored rose with tight coral buds swirling open to apricot-colored blossoms with luminous yellow centers. All the Rage blooms steadily all season so there is always a range of colors to enjoy. Blooms age to lipstick pink before dropping cleanly away. Add to that astonishingly clean, disease-resistant foliage and a perfectly round form, and you have an easy care rose that's truly All the Rage. Performs extremely well in cool and warm climates.Own root.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/all-the-rage-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyEleganceAlltheRage-01-4347-1-3-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>243</ID>
		<Title>Calypso Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Numerous delightful apricot blooms cover this compact mounded shrub rose. Dark glossy green foliage. Recurrent double blooms promise color throughout the season. An ideal accent for the garden or foundation planting. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/calypso-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/cacalypso-07-5454-1-3-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>263</ID>
		<Title>Champagne Wishes Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Clusters of soft apricot buds open fully to blooms of antique white with just a hint of apricot before fading to a clear white. Combines beautifully with perennials in a mixed border or plant as a refined low hedge. Disease-resistant medium green foliage. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/champagne-wishes-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/Champagne-Wishes_500x472.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>271</ID>
		<Title>Chi™ Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Chi™ has the most amazing clusters of truly red flowers. While small, they are double, and formed in large floribunda type heads creating a mass of color on a nicely compact shrub that gets up to 4’ in height. Bred at our farm in Oregon, Chi™ has always been a fantastic performer in the Pacific Northwest. The foliage is a dark green and like all Easy Elegance® roses is highly disease resistant. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/chi-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaChi-010-5425-01-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>275</ID>
		<Title>Como Park Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Great for beginners, this is one beautiful, tough rose. Como Park has consistently proven itself in Minnesota trials. Dark green foliage unfurls with a touch of red and stays clean all season long. Compact, rounded form will be covered from top to bottom in medium red, double blossoms. Plant in groups for a bright accent. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/como-park-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyEleganceComoParkmediumred-03-3710-1-3-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>284</ID>
		<Title>Coral Cove Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Incredible color, petite size, super disease resistant, what more could you want? This everblooming gem has double blooms whose outer petals are dark pink changing to orange and finally to bright yellow at the center. The small, perfectly rounded form would make it an outstanding informal hedge along a walkway or garden path. The color is so easy to combine it should have a place in every perennial border. Highly disease resistant and own root. Portland Rose Society Best Shrub Rose 2014.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/coral-cove-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyEleganceCoralCoveorangepink-01-4711-1-3-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>302</ID>
		<Title>Funny Face™ Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Pink and white painted blooms make this rose stand out from the crowd. No two flowers are quite the same. A prolific bloomer with a  compact, upright-to-rounded form and clean, disease-resistant foliage. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/funny-face-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/FunnyFace-010-2338-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>307</ID>
		<Title><![CDATA[Grandma's Blessing Rose]]></Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Resembling a hybrid tea, with large, full, dusty-pink blossoms, this beauty is so sweet we named it after Margaret 'Grandma' Bailey. Grandma's Blessing has a symmetrical, vase-shaped form and dark-green, disease-resistant foliage. Stunning color combines beautifully with many perennials. Also makes an elegant low hedge. Crown hardy in zone 4 with winter protection.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/grandmas-blessing-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyEleganceGrandmasBles-01-3292-1-3-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>316</ID>
		<Title>Head Over Heels Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Full, fluffy, light pink flowers bloom repeatedly through the summer. This upright rose, with dark, glossy-green foliage would make an excellent plant for the middle of a garden border. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/head-over-heels-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/heheadoverheels-01-5426-1-3-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>321</ID>
		<Title>High Voltage Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Shockingly beautiful clusters of double yellow blossoms are held high on sturdy canes. Super clean foliage complements the fragrant blooms. Upright, vase-shaped habit will stand up in the back of the border or stand out as an accent. Portland Rose Society Best Shrub Rose 2010. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/high-voltage-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyEleganceHighVoltagemyel-01-4366-1-3-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>328</ID>
		<Title>Kashmir Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Resembling a hybrid tea rose, the velvety red blossoms are as soft as cashmere and beg to be cut for the vase. With an evenly rounded habit, Kashmir fits perfectly into today's urban landscapes. Try this bold accent plant in the border, foundation or as a low hedge, hugging paths and walkways. Own root.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/kashmir-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyEleganceKashmirdarkred-01-4345-1-2-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>397</ID>
		<Title>Kiss Me Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Decidedly the most fragrant rose in the Easy Elegance® Collection, Kiss Me bears clusters of large, double, clear pink blooms, reminiscent of English roses. It blooms repeatedly through the growing season, and is especially attractive in the perennial border. Highly disease-resistant foliage adds to its appeal as a cut flower. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/kiss-me-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyEleganceKissMe-01-3297-1-3-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>406</ID>
		<Title>Little Mischief Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Let mischief reign in your garden with this compact everblooming rascal. New blooms of deep-pink with a white eye contrast nicely with the older, lighter pink blooms. With its glossy green foliage, low-growing habit and disease-resistant foliage, the only trouble this rose will get into will be with the rose it replaces in your garden. A wonderful companion plant in a border planting, a hedge plant or in a decorative container as the star performer. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/little-mischief-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/lilittlemischief-01-3305-1-3-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>412</ID>
		<Title><![CDATA[Macy's Pride™ Rose]]></Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[This delightful rose was selected by Macy's Department Store for their centennial. Lemon-yellow buds open fully to creamy-white and age gracefully with a hint of pink. Disease-resistant foliage, red-rimmed when immature, ages to a beautiful semi-glossy, medium green. Relatively thornless. New England Rose Society Award Winner in 2002. Own root.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/macys-pride-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyEleganceMacysPride-01-2566-1-2-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>424</ID>
		<Title>Music Box Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>An exhibition of color, Music Box sings with double blooms of creamy yellow centers surrounded by delicate pink blends. An everblooming mound of blossoms sits atop glossy medium green foliage that is resistant to disease. An ideal accent that will bring harmony to your garden. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/music-box-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyEleganceMusicBoxyellowblend-01-4968-1-3-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>447</ID>
		<Title>My Girl Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Adorable, round, deep pink buds are held in cluster of 5 to 30, opening to ruffly blossoms so full they almost hide the centers. Backed by medium green foliage, proven to be highly resistant to black spot with little to no defoliation. Compact, upright habit with good repeat bloom, My Girl makes a dazzling color statement in any border. Performs extremely well in both cool and warmer regions. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/my-girl-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyEleganceMyGirl-05-4660-1-3-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>461</ID>
		<Title>Mystic Fairy® Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Irresistible blooms of rich red with pink undertones carpet the plant in massive clusters all summer long. New foliage is glossy red, which slowly gives way to dark green mature leaves, a striking complement to the blooms. This compact, vigorous shrub rose is crown hardy to zone 4 and resistant to both blackspot and mildew. Mystic Fairy® has sterile flowers, produces no hips and doesn't know how to quit blooming. Own root.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/mystic-fairy-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyEleganceMysticFairy-01-2299-1-2-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>474</ID>
		<Title>Oscar Peterson™ Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Bred in Canada, and named after the famous Canadian jazz pianist and composer Oscar Peterson, this new rose is not only tough, it’s beautiful. Blooming from early summer through fall, the semi-double flowers start out a shade of soft yellow cream that soon turn to bright white with a contrasting center of golden yellow stamens. The flowers are arranged in sprays and the spent petals always fall cleanly from the plant. The foliage is dark rich green with excellent disease resistance. It has an upright habit, being slightly taller than wide. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/oscar-peterson-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/OscarPeterson-04-12751-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>479</ID>
		<Title>Paint the Town Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Wonderful clusters of red hybrid tea-shaped blooms carpet this rose from head to foot. Glossy, dark green foliage accents the red perfectly and highlights the incredible flower effect all season long. The even spreading-to-mounded habit is as well-suited to container gardening as it is to the border. Highly disease-resistant. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/paint-the-town-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyElegancePainttheTown-01-3885-1-3-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>487</ID>
		<Title>Pinktopia Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Pinktopia is an ideal accent or hedge plant. Masses of pink flowers are surrounded by dark green foliage and red new growth, creating a beautiful contrast. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/pinktopia-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyElegancePinktopiamedpink-01-4971-1-3-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>494</ID>
		<Title>Screaming Neon Red™ Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Intense color, superior performance. Screaming Neon Red™ is sure to be a standout for any garden. With vibrant flower power and repeat blooms throughout the season, this compact rose is the perfect choice as an accent or mass planting. Remarkably rich, disease-resistant, dark green foliage provides the perfect backdrop to neon-red blooms. Foliage turns a lovely burgundy-red in fall. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/screaming-neon-red-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyEleganceScreamingNeonRed-01-10341-1-3-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>509</ID>
		<Title>Snowdrift Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Like a snowdrift in summer, the habit is upright and amazingly uniform with blooms covering the plant all the way to the ground. Gorgeous, very full, cup-shaped blossoms of creamy white. With just a hint of apricot noticeable in the center, quite reminiscent of English roses. Each cluster of blossoms retains its pure color before dropping cleanly. This hardy, disease-resistant beauty is at home in any border and also makes a graceful hedge. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/snowdrift-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyEleganceSnowdrift-01-4657-1-3-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>520</ID>
		<Title>Sunrise Sunset Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>As the name implies, Sunrise Sunset is a stunning blend, with bright fuchsia-pink petals blending to apricot near the centers. Blue-green foliage is disease-resistant on this everblooming shrub rose. Its dense, spreading habit makes it an ideal ground cover and is also well suited to mass plantings. Performs extremley well in cooler and warmer regions of the country. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/sunrise-sunset-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyEleganceSunriseSunset-01-3294-1-3-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>529</ID>
		<Title>Super Hero Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[You don't have to be a Super Hero to grow great roses. Clusters of perfect, red blossoms stand out strongly against clean, medium to dark green, satiny foliage. Try this neat, compact, disease-resistant shrub in the border or foundation planting. Grows well in cooler and warmer regions. Own root.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/super-hero-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyEleganceSuperHero-01-4658-1-3-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>539</ID>
		<Title>Sweet Fragrance Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Hybrid tea-shaped buds in tropical tints of coral and orange with a deep yellow base swirl open to full, sweetly fragrant, apricot blossoms. Each bloom matures to salmon-pink, adding interest with the range of color. Clusters of buds and blooms are held on sturdy canes making them perfect for cutting. A vigorous, upright grower with excellent disease resistance. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/sweet-fragrance-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyEleganceSweetFragrance-01-4207-1-2-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>555</ID>
		<Title>Yellow Brick Road Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Neat, round, compact shrub covers itself with clusters of old-fashioned, lemon-yellow blossoms. Interestingly, the outer petals are slightly lighter in color. Blooms mature to butter-cream, extending the palate of colors. Excellent flower effect. Will add a splash of color in the front of the border, as a ground cover and also as a low hedge.  Excellent blackspot resistance, which is hard to find in yellow roses. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/yellow-brick-road-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyEleganceYellowBrickRd-01-4191-1-3-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>565</ID>
		<Title>Yellow Submarine Rose</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Clusters of bright lemon-yellow blossoms age to soft yellow and finally to white, creating a spectrum of yellows on one plant. This beauty has an upright habit and disease-resistant foliage. Most attractive planted in groups with other shrubs and perennials. Crown hardy in zone 4 with mulch for winter protection. Own root.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://easyeleganceroses.com/product/yellow-submarine-rose/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://easyeleganceroses.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RosaEasyEleganceYelSubmarine-01-3704-1-3-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
</data>