<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<post>
		<ID>676</ID>
		<Title>Blushing Bride Reblooming Hydrangea</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA['Blushing Bride' has big round clusters of pure white, semi-double florets, which mature to blush pink or Carolina blue, depending on soil pH. Internodes between the leaves are shorter than on the The Original, making it more compact and stronger stemmed. Like the other Endless Summer® varieties, 'Blushing Bride' blooms on old and new growth and is remarkably mildew resistant. Long a favorite in Europe, 'Blushing Bride' is excellent for cut flowers and for blending louder colors in the garden. (CPBR3403)]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://endlesssummerhydrangeas.com/product/blushing-bride-reblooming-hydrangea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://endlesssummerhydrangeas.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/ES_BlushingBride.png</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>690</ID>
		<Title>The Original Reblooming Hydrangea</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[A Bailey Nurseries introduction, The Original is a mop-head type hydrangea with the unique ability to bloom consistently on both old and new wood. The result is a plant that provides beautiful flowers all summer long. The flowers grow up to 8" in diameter, with pink blooms in alkaline soils and blue blooms in acidic soil. Since The Original blooms on new wood, removal of spent flowers will encourage rebloom. (CPBR2305, C®)]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://endlesssummerhydrangeas.com/product/the-original-reblooming-hydrangea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://endlesssummerhydrangeas.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/ES_The-Original.png</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>706</ID>
		<Title>BloomStruck® Reblooming Hydrangea</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[BloomStruck®, part of the Endless Summer® Collection, is another breeding breakthrough. After 50 days below 0° F, and a low of -28° F, BloomStruck® flowered heavily the following spring on old growth and put out loads of blooms on new growth. In addition to being cold tolerant, BloomStruck's glossy dark green leaves are more heat resistant, which prevents wilting in mid-day heat. This reblooming mophead has rounded flowers averaging 3.5 - 5" across in intense rose-pink, violet or blue, depending on pH levels. Flower heads are held upright on striking ruby red stems, adding to this plant's retail presence. (C®)]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://endlesssummerhydrangeas.com/product/bloomstruck-reblooming-hydrangea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://endlesssummerhydrangeas.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/ES_BloomStruck.png</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>729</ID>
		<Title>Summer Crush® Reblooming Hydrangea</Title>
		<baileyDescription>It’s not just about blue or pink anymore! The intense, deep coloration found in Summer Crush® is a true differentiator in the hydrangea marketplace. With a profusion of big raspberry red or neon purple blooms, Summer Crush® is a color breakthrough in reblooming garden hydrangeas and a welcome addition to the Endless Summer® brand. Introduced by Bailey Innovations, this new addition is the result of focused breeding and years of production and field testing. Proven to be Zone 4 cold hardy and the most wilt resistant Endless Summer® yet, this compact growing hydrangea with dark green glossy leaves fits smaller spaces in the garden and is the perfect size for patio containers. CPBRAF, ®CA</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://endlesssummerhydrangeas.com/product/summer-crush-reblooming-hydrangea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://endlesssummerhydrangeas.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/ES_SummerCrush.png</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>751</ID>
		<Title>Twist-n-Shout® Reblooming Hydrangea</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Like all plants in the Endless Summer® Collection, Twist-n-Shout® produces abundant blooms on both old and new wood all summer long. Lacy centers are surrounded by gorgeous blossoms of pink or periwinkle blue, depending on soil type. Sturdy red stems and glossy deep green leaves turn red-burgundy in fall to offer year-round interest in the garden. Easy to care for and hardy to zone 4, Twist-n-Shout® is an elegant stand-alone specimen, dramatic in combination with other plants, and compact enough for containers. (CPBR3688, C®)</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://endlesssummerhydrangeas.com/product/twist-n-shout-reblooming-hydrangea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://endlesssummerhydrangeas.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/ES_Twist-n-Shout.png</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>11193</ID>
		<Title>Pop Star® Reblooming Hydrangea</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Genetically compact and incredibly floriferous, Pop Star® Hydrangea is a lacecap variety that is a standout in the landscape or decorative container. With strong bud hardiness and reliable rebloom, Pop Star® is a blooming powerhouse. Its short stature makes this a strong border or short hedge plant that doesn’t need pruning to keep its size and is great for year-after-year color on your deck, patio, or porch. The dark green leaves against the blue or pink blooms give the classic hydrangea look, while the lacecap flowers add extra texture and interest to the garden.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://endlesssummerhydrangeas.com/product/pop-star-reblooming-hydrangea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://endlesssummerhydrangeas.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Pop-Star_500x472_.png</ImageFeatured>
	</post>
</data>