<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<post>
		<ID>325</ID>
		<Title>Matador™ Maple</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Selected because of its superior habit and fall color, Matador™ turns deeper red than Autumn Blaze® and colors more consistently than Sienna Glen®. An adaptable tree with an upright, symmetrical form. Gains its fall color a bit later than other cultivars and holds its leaves longer. Excellent choice for lawn, street or park. Discovered in 1997 at our container tree farm by Kevin Johnston of Bailey Nurseries, Inc.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/matador-maple/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/AcerxfreeFirstEditionsMatador-10-3207-1-2-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>331</ID>
		<Title>Parkland Pillar® Birch</Title>
		<baileyDescription>A beautiful birch with a narrow, upright, dense habit. It boasts white bark and dense, dark green foliage that turns golden in late fall. This fast growing variety is suitable for gardens, screens or boulevards. Tolerant of heat  and alkaline soils, Parkland Pillar™ is an excellent choice for urban landscapes. Its narrow form makes it perfect as an accent tree or it can be planted in multiples to form a privacy screen. This selection of Dakota Pinnacle® was found at Parkland Nurseries in Alberta in 2006.(CPBR #4513,®CA)</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/parkland-pillar-birch/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/BetulaParklandPillar-033-9680-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>3,4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>341</ID>
		<Title>Bali™ Hibiscus-Tree Form</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Tree form is perfect for small landscapes or as a specimen plant. Semi-double pure white flowers are highlighted with a bold purple red center from July-September. Bred by Minier Nursery in France.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/bali-hibiscus-tree-form/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HibiscussyriacusFirstEditionsBalitree-01-9255-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>343</ID>
		<Title>Fiji™ Hibiscus-Tree Form</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Tree form is ideal for small landscapes or as a specimen plant. Buds are medium pink and give way to semi-double flowers which slowly fade to light pink. A splash of deep red colors the center. Blooms from July-September. Bred by Minier Nursery in France.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/fiji-hibiscus-tree-form/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HibiscusFirstEditionsFiji-12-9256-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>347</ID>
		<Title>Tahiti™ Hibiscus-Tree Form</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Tree form is perfect for small landscapes or as a specimen plant. Gorgeous semi-double blooms from July-October. Deep pink-purple flowers are accentuated with a deep red center. Bred by Minier Nursery in France.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/tahiti-hibiscus-tree-form/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HibiscusTahitiTree-004-9254-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>349</ID>
		<Title>French Cabaret™ Blush Hibiscus</Title>
		<baileyDescription>French Cabaret™ Blush in tree form is a knockout standard with sterile doubles from French breeder Corinne Liquiere at Minier Nursery in France. Dark pink flower buds open to a delicate blush pink with shades of white. Large, double, pompom flowers bloom profusely from July to October. Heat tolerant, drought tolerant and adapted to alkaline soils.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/french-cabaret-blush-hibiscus-2/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HibsyrFirstEdiFrenchCabaretBlush-03-12762-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>351</ID>
		<Title>Berry White® Hydrangea-Tree Form</Title>
		<baileyDescription>This long-awaited introduction is a step forward in paniculata breeding. With strong, upright stems and large cone-shaped flower panicles that stay upright, this plant is a summer stunner. The flower color starts out white in July then progresses to dark pink, beginning at the bottom and developing up to the top of the panicle. Berry White® blooms a little later than Strawberry Sundae® and about the same time as Vanilla Strawberry™. Color shades can vary by location, climate, and type of soil. This tree-form hydrangea is perfect for garden focal points or containers.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/berry-white-hydrangea-tree-form/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HydBerryWhite-121-12116-01-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>354</ID>
		<Title>Vanilla Strawberry™ - Tree Form</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Now available in tree form, perfect for small landscapes or urban gardens. The enormous flower panicles are a blend of vanilla and strawberry, held upright on red stems. They emerge creamy white in mid-summer, change to pink and finally to strawberry red. New blooms give the plant a multicolored effect in late summer and early fall. The red coloration persists for at least 3-4 weeks. Introduced by Bailey Nurseries.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/vanilla-strawberry-tree-form/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HydrangeaFEVanillaStrawberrytree-03-9670-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>360</ID>
		<Title>Centennial Blush  Star Magnolia</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Pink buds open to incredibly full and wonderfully fragrant pale pink flowers in spring. Centennial Blush™ is a prolific bloomer with flower buds formed at almost every node yielding a fantastic floral display of delicate pink covering the entire plant. Blooms just as reliably in St. Paul, Minnesota as in Athens, Georgia. Centennial Blush™ is also well adapted to a variety of soils. Attractive medium green foliage on an interesting branching structure follows in summer, turning yellow to bronze in autumn. Can be grown as a large shrub or a small tree, perfectly suited for small urban gardens. Bred by Michael Dirr of the University of Georgia.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/centennial-blush-star-magnolia/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/MagnoliaFirstEditionCentennialBlush-01-5696-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>372</ID>
		<Title>Gladiator™ Crabapple</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Gladiator™ is an excellent ornamental tree with a profusion of bright pink flowers followed by small reddish-purple fruit on a stately, upright crown. Glossy bronze-purple leaves are darker and glossier than Purple Prince, remain lush all season long and are highly disease resistant.  Gladiator is an ideal ornamental tree for space-challenged sites including under power lines, as a small boulevard tree or planted in a row for a screen. This is an open pollinated selection of 'Royalty'. Selected by Rick Durand, from Portage la Prairie MB, CA. (®CA)]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/gladiator-crabapple/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/MalusFirstEditionsGladiatorCrab-01-6570-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>2,3,4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>377</ID>
		<Title>Ruby Tears™ Crabapple</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Red buds open to fragrant pink flowers which completely engulf the cascading branches each spring. This naturally weeping crab has a habit similar to 'Louisa' and burgundy-green foliage like 'Prairifire'. Attractive dark red fruit lasts into mid-winter. This seedling was found at Beverly Nursery in Indiana.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/ruby-tears-crabapple/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/MalusRubyTears-244-2848.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>387</ID>
		<Title>Amber Jubilee™ Ninebark- Tree Form</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Now available in tree form.  Selected for its striking foliage in glowing tones of orange, yellow and gold. With its bold array of colors, it will stand out as a lovely focal point in a small garden landscape. Delicate white blooms are produced in spring, and fall foliage is highlighted with tones of red and purple, making this ninebark appealing over the entire season. Plant in full sun for best performance. Seedling selection of Diabolo® and Dart's Gold Ninebark.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/amber-jubilee-ninebark-tree-form/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/PhysoopFirstEditionsAmberJubilee-01-10544-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>2,3,4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>390</ID>
		<Title>Majestic Skies™ Northern Pin Oak</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Majestic Skies™ is a distinct improvement over the species with straighter branching and a more symmetrical shape. Foliage emerges red in spring and is more substantial and darker green than the species. Excellent red fall color. Northern pin oaks prefer to grow in full sun with deep, well-drained soil. Discovered at Bailey Nurseries.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/majestic-skies-northern-pin-oak/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/QuercusellipFirstEditionsMajesticSkies-48-2876-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>3,4,5,6</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>393</ID>
		<Title>Snowdance™ Japanese Tree Lilac</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Although the species tend to flower biennially, Snowdance™ flowers well annually and begins flowering at an earlier age than the species. It has exceptionally heavy bloom with large, fragrant, creamy white flower clusters in June. This variety produces few untidy brown seedheads. Lustrous dark green foliage is slightly larger and darker than the species.
Snowdance™ grows as wide as it is tall with attractive, shelved branching. A pest-and-disease-free lilac tree, it is ideal for residential and park use and is equally attractive as a specimen as it is in group plantings. Selected by Rod Bailey for its remarkably heavy bloom.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/snowdance-japanese-tree-lilac/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/SyringaretFirstEditionsSnowdance-02-3034-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>3,4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>397</ID>
		<Title>St Croix™ American Elm</Title>
		<baileyDescription>St. Croix™ elm is a new and distinct American elm with good tolerance to Dutch elm disease. With a grand, vase shape and an open, spreading canopy, St. Croix™ promises to revitalize this well-loved shade tree. Its summer foliage is a beautiful dark green with fall foliage turning a wonderful yellow. The selection is a clone from a tree in Minnesota that survived in a stand of DED-infected elms for over 35 years. In testing at the University of Minnesota, St. Croix shows very good DED tolerance in repeated field trials with controlled inoculation. Selected by Chris Bliska.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/st-croix-american-elm/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/UlmusamFirstEditionsStCroix-03-5932-1.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>3,4,5,6</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>404</ID>
		<Title>Standing Ovation™ Serviceberry</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Standing Ovation™ is covered in white flowers each spring, which often turn into edible berries in June. As the seasons continue, dark green, almost circular leaves change to red and orange in autumn. Its upright, perfectly oval form adds height in small gardens, and provides nice structure during winter. Standing Ovation™ is a good alternative to columnar buckthorn. The uniform habit makes it great for hedging. From Valk Plants in the Netherlands.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/standing-ovation-serviceberry/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/AmelStandingOvation-043-3197.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>2,3,4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>420</ID>
		<Title>Cabernet® Barberry</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[This extremely dense, compact form of 'Crimson Pygmy' does not require pruning and is more winter hardy. Bright crimson new growth is followed by rich burgundy to purple foliage. From R & V Moretti Nursery.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/cabernet-barberry/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/BerbthunFirstEditionsCabernetBarb-08-5545-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>431</ID>
		<Title>Lambrusco™ Barberry</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Densely arranged leaves coupled with a spreading habit make this barberry a useful landscape plant. The foliage emerges red and deepens to burgundy as the season progresses. Can be used instead of 'Crimson Pygmy' in colder climates since it is more cold hardy. Bred by Don Selinger and introduced by Bailey Nurseries.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/lambrusco-barberry/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/BerbthunFirstEditionsLambrusco-04-8762-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>438</ID>
		<Title>Limoncello™ Barberry</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Forming a tidy, round mound, this barberry has chartreuse foliage with an unusual red, almost dotted pattern around the leaf margin through July in Minnesota. Fall foliage is orange, yellow and red. The bright color and habit make it a good accent plant in foundation plantings. Bred by Don Selinger and introduced by Bailey Nurseries.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/limoncello-barberry/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/BerbthunFirstEditionsLimoncello-01-7272-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>453</ID>
		<Title>Toscana™ Barberry</Title>
		<baileyDescription>The large showy foliage emerges red in spring with a fine, bright yellow margin. The margin eventually fades through summer, but the foliage remains a good red. The leaf color darkens in autumn, taking on flaming scarlet tones. Forms an upright shrub with arching branches. Bred by Don Selinger and introduced by Bail</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/toscana-barberry/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/BerbthunFirstEditionsToscana-07-4952-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>464</ID>
		<Title>Funky Fuchsia™ Butterfly Bush</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Rounded to upright habit with dark green foliage, gray beneath. The habit is more upright than 'Miss Molly' and 'Miss Ruby'. Rich reddish-pink inflorescences are very upright and quite fragrant, providing loads of nectar for pollinators. Showy flowers average 6-10” long on vigorous shoots.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/funky-fuchsia-butterfly-bush/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/BuddleiaFirstEditionsFunkyFuchsia-07-11401-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>473</ID>
		<Title>Groovy Grape™ Butterfly Bush</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Rounded to upright habit with arching 8-10" long inflorescences. Rich, violet-purple flowers are fragrant. Bred by Plant Introductions, Inc.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/groovy-grape-butterfly-bush/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/BuddleiaFirstEditionsGroovyGrape-03-11638-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>480</ID>
		<Title>Psychedelic Sky™ Butterfly Bush</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Well matched with Funky Fuchsia™ in habit and flower display, Psychedelic Sky™ has strong upright stems supporting clear blue. Flowers average 6-10” long on and are filled with nectar for pollinators. The habit is upright and tidy, like Funky Fuchsia™.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/psychedelic-sky-butterfly-bush/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/BuddleiaFirstEditionsPsychedelicSky-12-11400-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>488</ID>
		<Title>Sapphire Surf™ Bluebeard</Title>
		<baileyDescription>This compact, low-maintenance shrub produces a swell of stunning blue flowers from top to bottom in late summer and fall when few other plants are blooming. These late bloomers a boost for shoulder season sales as well as migrating pollinators. The habit is lower growing than most Caryopteris so it makes a colorful groundcover. Sapphire Surf™ is deer and drought resistant. Selected
by Kordes Nursery in Germany.
</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/sapphire-surf-bluebeard/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/cacaryopterissapphiresurf-01-6552-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>505</ID>
		<Title>Fiber Optics® Buttonbush</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Fiber Optics® is a distinct improvement over the coarser species that grows twice the size of this compact selection. Native from Florida to Mexico and north to Nova Scotia and Ontario, buttonbush is quite happy in moist conditions, tolerating flooding and wet spring soil. As such it is often used in wetland restoration work, along streams and pond banks. It’s an ideal choice for low areas in the landscape that stay moist. Conversely, it grows well without excessive moisture. Fiber Optics® has exceptional wildlife benefits including nectar filled flowers and the seed is eaten by waterfowl.
</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/fiber-optics-buttonbush/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/cecephalanthusburnsyflower-01-4963-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>517</ID>
		<Title>Neon Burst™ Dogwood</Title>
		<baileyDescription>This new Tatarian dogwood from Bylands Nursery in British Columbia has attractive chartreuse foliage and is a compact selection growing 4-5’ tall. It has good sun and heat tolerance, retaining bright leaf color throughout summer. New leaves are tinged with bronze and the stems have a rich red hue early in the season. Fall foliage becomes a rainbow of purple, red, yellow and orange.
In winter the stems turn glossy scarlet red. Unlike most C. alba, Neon Burst™ works well as a specimen plant or in large groupings. (®CA)
</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/neon-burst-dogwood/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/CornusNeonBurst-02-12118-1.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>2,3,4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>524</ID>
		<Title>Firedance™ Dogwood</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Firedance™ is similar to 'Isanti' but has a much more compact, uniform habit. Our trials also show Firedance™ has fewer problems than the species. White flowers in spring are followed by pretty white berries that are attractive to birds. The foliage turns a nice red-purple color in fall followed by red stems in winter, giving multi-season interest. It is tolerant of moist conditions, is suitable for rain gardens and good on slopes to hold soil in place. Discovered by Terry Schwartz of Bailey Nurseries.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/firedance-dogwood/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/CornusFirstEditionsFiredance-01-4819-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>2,3,4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>535</ID>
		<Title>Autumn Inferno® Cotoneaster</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Discovered at Bron & Sons Nursery in British Columbia, this new Cotoneaster is a natural cross between C. lucidus and C. apiculatus. It has many of the attributes of C. lucidus that we so love for a hedge - great form, easily pruned, great foliage all season long plus great fall color. But what we really love about Autumn Inferno™ is the small red berries formed along the stems in fall. The berries stay on the plant until the birds come and take them, no mess involved. Perfect as a pruned formal hedge or let it go natural.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/autumn-inferno-cotoneaster/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/CotoneasterAutumnInferno-012-13130-1-t-m.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>540</ID>
		<Title>Cool Splash® Dwarf Bush Honeysuckle</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Cool Splash®, the first variegated Diervilla, has bright white leaf margins that remain bright and clean until the first frost. Bunches of yellow blossoms adorn the plant in June and July. Easy to grow in a variety of soils as long as the soil is not bone dry. Cool Splash® is a densely branched shrub that forms underground suckers, developing colonies over time. Use in lightly shaded areas or mass plantings in full sun for a spectacular effect. Found by Peter Podaras.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/cool-splash-dwarf-bush-honeysuckle/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/DiervillaFirstEditionsCoolSplashPP19391-24-5290-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>554</ID>
		<Title>Cinnamon Girl® Distylium</Title>
		<baileyDescription>With smaller foliage and a more refined look than other distylium on the market, Cinnamon Girl® is an excellent alternative to boxwood and other evergreen plants beleaguered by insects and diseases in the south. Plum-purple new growth turns to blue-green as the leaves mature. This plant really shines in the landscape so put a few in the ground where staff and customers can see it mature. Definitely our most cold hardy distylium to date,  it came through the 2015 winter with no burn while other varieties had moderate to severe dieback. (CPBRAF)</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/cinnamon-girl-distylium/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/DistyliumFirstEditionsCinnamonGirl-06-11999-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>563</ID>
		<Title>Coppertone™ Distylium</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Coppertone™ features coppery-red new foliage that matures to a cool blue-green. At 3-4’ tall and 4-5’ wide, it is a good mid-size choice for landscape beds.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/coppertone-distylium/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/DistyliumFirstEditionsCoppertone-01-11255-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>571</ID>
		<Title>Linebacker™ Distylium</Title>
		<baileyDescription>This upright evergreen takes on the shape of a white oak whiskey barrel in youth and matures into an excellent screening or hedge plant. Reddish new growth matures to lustrous dark green. Foliage does not thin out in the center of the plant. With no pests or diseases to trouble it, Linebacker™ is becoming a popular replacement for cherrylaurel for screening and hedges. Impressive in #7 and larger containers.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/linebacker-distylium/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/didistyliumlinebacker-01-11637-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>582</ID>
		<Title>Swing Low® Distylium</Title>
		<baileyDescription>We selected Swing Low™  because it makes a perfect prostrate groundcover. Low growing at 2-3’ tall and spreading 4-6’ wide, with blue-green leaves densely arranged on horizontal branches. Like all First Editions® distylium, Swing Low™ is an adaptable plant that can be used in multiple landscape applications. It adapts well to pruning and is disease and insect resistant.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/swing-low-distylium/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/didistyliyumswinglow-01-12791-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>585</ID>
		<Title>Vintage Jade Distylium</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Vintage Jade was the first Distylium in First Editions® and has become one of the best-selling plants in the south. This remarkable plant is bulletproof and perfectly suited for large scale landscapes as well as homeowner use. This variety has layered branches and forms an intermediate spreading mound in the landscape, making it perfect for covering large areas. Lustrous dark green foliage looks good all season long.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/vintage-jade-distylium/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/DistyliumFirstEditionsVintageJade-01-11061-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>597</ID>
		<Title>Lotus Moon™ Pearlbush</Title>
		<baileyDescription>This spring bloomer is covered in white round flower buds resembling a string of pearls. Buds open to clear white blooms that completely cover the plant in April and May, attracting early butter?ies. Flowers are borne on previous year’s growth so prune right after ?owering. Lotus Moon™ has bright green foliage on compact, upright, mounded plants. Deer resistant and low maintenance in the landscape, it grows well from Minnesota to Georgia. Bred by Don Selinger and introduced by Bailey Nurseries.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/lotus-moon-pearlbush/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/ExochordamaFirstEditionsLotusMooon-176-4825.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>3,4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>609</ID>
		<Title>Sweet Tea™ Gardenia</Title>
		<baileyDescription>This cross between Double Mint and Pinwheel™ produced a plant with the best features of both parents. With tennis ball sized double flowers and excellent cold hardiness this heavy rebloomer has elegant, densely scented ?owers. At 3-5’ tall and wide, Sweet Tea™ is more upright and larger than Double Mint. It is also more winter hardy. In 2013-2014 this selection survived 4-6°F in an above ground container with no injury. That’s saying something since many other gardenias suffered severe damage during the same winter. Bred by Plant Introductions, Inc.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/sweet-tea-gardenia/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/gagardeniasweettea-02-11724-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>623</ID>
		<Title>Double Mint Gardenia</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Compact, rounded growth habit with double 2” fragrant flowers that bloom all summer long. No other double comes close to matching Double Mint in rebloom capacity. Lustrous dark foliage. Double Mint grows to a maximum of 3’ in height and spread, making this compact plant perfect for smaller spaces and containers where the fragrance can be enjoyed at close range. Makes an excellent retail presentation. Bred by Plant Introductions, Inc.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/double-mint-gardenia/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/gardeniajasmonoidesdoublemint_2.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>633</ID>
		<Title>Sweet Star® Gardenia</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Blooming into late summer and early fall, Sweet Star® is covered in single flowers starting early May. Excellent rebloom throughout summer. Flowers are followed by pretty orange fruit. Plants are nicely rounded with glossy green leaves and stay very compact in habit. Sweet Star® originated from cold hardy wild collected Gardenia jasminoides seed from the Beijing Botanical Garden. Reliably cold hardy in zone 7, it came through the record-setting 2013-14 winter in Athens, GA with minimal frost damage. Makes up quickly in production. Bred by Plant Introductions, Inc.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/sweet-star-gardenia/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/GardeniaSweetStar-32-11183-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>651</ID>
		<Title>Tianshan® Seven-son flower</Title>
		<baileyDescription>While bred in France, this new cultivar is named after the mountain range in China where the species is native. Clusters of fragrant, creamy-white flowers appear in late summer, with each whorl containing 7 flowers. The blooms are followed in autumn by unusual purplish-red fruits. What makes this variety unique is its compact habit, growing only 8-12’, spreading only 5-7’. This small plant is well branched and forms a rounded, upright shrub or small tree with dark green shiny foliage that turns yellow in late fall. Exfoliating bark is very attractive in the winter. Use as a feature plant or as an informal hedge.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/tianshan-seven-son-flower/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HeptacodiumTianshan-002-10073-01-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>660</ID>
		<Title>Bali™ Hibiscus</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Semi-double pure white flowers are highlighted with a bold purple-red center. Flowers are 3-4" in diameter. Bred by Minier Nursery in France.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/bali-hibiscus/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HibiscussyriacusFirstEditionsBalitree-01-9255-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>669</ID>
		<Title>Fiji™ Hibiscus</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Medium pink buds give way to 3” to 4” flowers with a unique pattern, which slowly fades to light pink. A splash of deep red colors the center. Bred by Minier Nursery in France.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/fiji-hibiscus/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HibiscusFirstEditionsFiji-02-6898-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>676</ID>
		<Title>Hawaii™ Hibiscus</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Large showy blossoms 3-4" diameter are a lovely blue accentuated with a red-purple heart. Bred  by Minier Nursery in France.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/hawaii-hibiscus/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HibiscussyrFirstEditionsHawaii-11-7928-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>683</ID>
		<Title>French Cabaret™ Blush Hibiscus</Title>
		<baileyDescription>French Cabaret™ is the first in a series of sterile doubles from French breeder Corinne Liquiere at Minier Nursery in France. Dark pink flower buds open to a delicate blush pink with shades of white. Large, double, pompom flowers bloom profusely from July to October. Compact in size with an upright habit. Heat tolerant, drought tolerant and adapted to alkaline soils. Appears to set very little viable seed.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/french-cabaret-blush-hibiscus/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HibsyrFirstEdiFrenchCabaretBlush-021-10066-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>693</ID>
		<Title>French Cabaret™ Red Hibiscus</Title>
		<baileyDescription>This is the second double Hibiscus from Minier Nursery. Like its cousin, French Cabaret™ Blush, it is upright in habit and a vigorous grower. For eight weeks in summer, French Cabaret™ Red has clusters of three to five richly saturated red double flowers that resemble carnations. Deep red flower buds open to 2” diameter pompom flowers with sterile seed.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/french-cabaret-red-hibiscus/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HibiscusFrenchCaberetRed-019-11354-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>704</ID>
		<Title>Tahiti™ Hibiscus</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Semi-double deep pink-purple flowers are accentuated with a deep red center. Blooms July-September with 3-4" diameter flowers bringing welcome color to the summer landscape. Bred by Minier Nursery in France.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/tahiti-hibiscus/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HibiscussyrFirstEditionsTahiti-037-6479-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>709</ID>
		<Title>Light-O-Day® Hydrangea</Title>
		<baileyDescription>This elegant lacecap hydrangea stands out with remarkably refined, pure white variegation. The flower heads have a ring of bright white sterile flowers while the inner blooms are glowing blue or pink depending on soil pH. The dramatic blooms coupled with clean, bright foliage naturally draw attention and make this an outstanding feature plant in the garden or in containers. Selected by Bailey Nurseries.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/light-o-day-hydrangea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HydmaFirstEditionsLightODay-22-4250-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>721</ID>
		<Title>Berry White® Panicle Hydrangea</Title>
		<baileyDescription>This long-awaited introduction is a step forward in paniculata breeding. With strong, upright stems and large cone-shaped flower panicles that stay upright, this plant is a summer stunner. Like the other paniculatas from Mr. Renault at Pépinières Renault, the flower color starts out white in July then progresses to dark pink. Coloring occurs from the bottom and progresses to the top of the panicle. Berry White® blooms a little later than Strawberry Sundae® and about the same time as Vanilla Strawberry™. Color shades can vary according to location, climate and type of soil. Our growers like this plant, and we think you will, too. (CPBR 6046), ®CA</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/berry-white-panicle-hydrangea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HydBerryWhite-002-10091-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>3,4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>732</ID>
		<Title>Diamond Rouge® Panicle Hydrangea</Title>
		<baileyDescription>This variety has abundant, long lasting, rounded flower heads that start white and progress to pink, intense raspberry red and finally wine red. Flowers start blooming in July and take on red coloration earlier in the season than other pink paniculatas. Flower color is best in the fall when night temperatures are 10 degrees cooler than day temperatures. Compared to Strawberry Sundae®, Diamond Rouge® is slightly bigger and has distinct raspberry-red flowers that color earlier in the season. Benefits from multiple prunes in production to produce strong stems. Flower color varies based on climate and growing conditions. Bred by Jean Renault in France. (CPBRAF, ®CA)</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/diamond-rouge-panicle-hydrangea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HydpanFirstEditionsDiamondRouge-01-10088-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>3,4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>743</ID>
		<Title>Strawberry Sundae®Panicle Hydrangea</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Strawberry Sundae® is another outstanding selection from French breeder Jean Renault. This compact selection is similar to Vanilla Strawberry™ but much more compact. Flowers emerge creamy white in mid- summer and change to pink as night temperatures cool down. With its compact habit this hydrangea adds striking flowers to small spaces and is nicely proportioned for patio containers. The color lasts well into fall. Excellent for fresh cut and dried flower arrangements. Flower color varies based on climate and growing conditions. (CPBR #4609)</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/strawberry-sundaepanicle-hydrangea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HydFirstEditionsStrawberrySundae-61-10089-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>3,4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>762</ID>
		<Title>Vanilla Strawberry™ Panicle Hydrangea</Title>
		<baileyDescription>The enormous flower heads are a blend of vanilla and strawberry, held upright on red stems. Flowers emerge creamy white in midsummer, change to pink as the night temperatures drop and finally turn strawberry red. New blooms emerge as older blooms change color, giving the plant a multicolored effect in late summer and early fall. The red coloring lasts at least 3-4 weeks. Plants grow upright, then cascade later in the season. Excellent for fresh cut and dried flower arrangements. Flower color varies based on climate and growing conditions. Bred by Jean Renault in France. (CPBR #3963)</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/vanilla-strawberry-hydrangea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HydFirstEditionsVanillaStrawberry-11-5778-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>3,4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>

	<post>
		<ID>776</ID>
		<Title>White Diamonds® Panicle Hydrangea</Title>
		<baileyDescription>With a commanding presence in the summer and fall garden, White Diamonds® is an exceptional compact hydrangea with glistening white panicles that are held upright and eventually fade to parchment and pink. Smaller and more manageable than most H. paniculata, White Diamonds® boasts dark green leathery foliage that displays increased heat and drought tolerance. Use as an anchor in the mixed border, plant as a hedge, or in a large grouping for a magnificent effect. Bred by Dr. Michael Dirr at the University of Georgia.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/white-diamonds-panicle-hydrangea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HydrangeapanWhiteDiamond-01-4827-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>3,4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>790</ID>
		<Title>Jetstream™ Hydrangea</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Jetstream™ is a quantum leap in oakleaf hydrangea introductions with a dense, compact, non-flopping habit. The lustrous dark green foliage is resistant to leaf spot and turns fantastic orange-red in autumn. Flowers, held high on strong stems, are a beautiful white aging to pink. Jetstream™ is a classic native flowering shrub for the garden, grouping and massing. Exfoliating tawny-brown bark adds winter interest, as do the dried flower heads. Bred by Plant Introductions, Inc.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/jetstream-hydrangea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HydquerFirstEditionsJetstream-01-11090-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>802</ID>
		<Title>Cobalt-n-Gold™ Hypericum</Title>
		<baileyDescription>This mounded grower has blue-silver foliage blanketed with 3/4” sunny yellow flowers in late spring and early summer. In fall, the leaves transform to yellow, orange, and red and reveal an attractive exfoliating bark. This plant thrives in full sun and well-drained soil and is adaptable in many parts of the country, growing reliably from Georgia to Minnesota. Good alternative to spirea and potentilla in colder areas of the country. Bred by Plant Introductions, Inc.
</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/cobalt-n-gold-hypericum/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HyperFirstEditionsCobaltnGold-09-11256-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>811</ID>
		<Title>Pumpkin Hypericum</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Pumpkin Hypercium is covered with yellow flowers in spring, followed by clusters of glowing orange berries each fall, making them the perfect addition to cut autumn floral arrangements. Plant in mixed containers along with fall mums or flowering kale to highlight its outstanding fall berry display, or in the garden in drifts where it can truly show off its multi-season appeal. Rust-resistant and easy to grow.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/pumpkin-hypericum/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/HypericuminodFirstEditionsPumpkin-022-10430-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>6,7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>826</ID>
		<Title>Chubby Hubby™ Japanese Holly</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Chubby Hubby™ Ilex is best described as Ernie to Straight & Narrow® Japanese Holly’s Bert, with similar leaves and strong upright branches yet it is considerably wider and more oval in habit than its counterpart. The dad-bod features of this holly are perfectly suited for evergreen hedging, replacing boxwoods and other evergreens that are plagued by diseases, insects, or are weak stemmed. Leaves are flat, do not cup, and remain a shiny dark green all winter. Male. Bred by Dr. Michael Dirr at the University of Georgia.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/chubby-hubby-japanese-holly/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/IlexcrenataChubbyHubby-012-13235-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>827</ID>
		<Title><![CDATA[Straight & Narrow® Japanese Holly]]></Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[We’ve been trialing this Japanese holly a long time to be certain it lives up to its name. Straight & Narrow® is exactly that. Growing 6’ tall and 18’ wide, Straight & Narrow® is so much better than 'Sky Pencil' and 'Sky Sentry'. This plant has strong branches that remain upright and don’t splay out as it ages or faces the elements. Leaves are flat, not cupped, shiny dark green and remain nice looking through winter. Male. Destined to become THE columnar Japanese holly of choice for retail and landscape. Bred by Plant Introductions, Inc.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/straight-narrow-japanese-holly/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/IlexStraightandNarrow-01-11989-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>830</ID>
		<Title>Wildfire™ Winterberry</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Female selection with dark green foliage and abundantly large,bright red fruit. Fall and early winter provides stems ideal for floral or seasonal displays. Rounded habit creates a wonderful foundation plant, specimen or hedge. Jim Dandy is needed for pollination. A selection by Gordie Bailey and introduced by Bailey Nurseries.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/wildfire-winterberry/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/IlexvertFirstEditionsWildfire-01-3216-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>840</ID>
		<Title>BananAppeal® Small Anise Tree</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[This compact, well-behaved Illicium has golden-yellow foliage and keeps a nice mounded form as it ages. Leaves are wider than 'Florida Sunshine' and it’s a better grower in production. Unlike 'Florida Sunshine', BananAppeal® doesn’t send out long gangly shoots, and plants are more compact and disease resistant. With anise-scented foliage, it is a perfect accent plant in shade gardens, maintaining its small stature and luminescent yellow-gold foliage. No suckers to date. Bred by Plant Introductions, Inc.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/bananappeal-small-anise-tree/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/ililliciumfirsteditionsbananappeal-06-12274-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>851</ID>
		<Title>Pink Frost Florida Anise Tree</Title>
		<baileyDescription>A vigorous evergreen shrub for shady locations, Pink Frost has lovely variegated white and green foliage that turns rosy-pink in cold weather. Maroon-red ?owers bloom for 4-6 weeks in spring. The foliage has a pleasant gin and tonic scent. Loves moist, but well-drained soils. Introduced by Plant Introductions, Inc.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/pink-frost-florida-anise-tree/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/IlliciumFirstEditionsPinkFrost-35-10206-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>861</ID>
		<Title>Love Child® Sweetspire</Title>
		<baileyDescription>A small form of Virginia Sweetspire, blooming in spring with white racemes radiating out from a rounded plant with bright green foliage. We selected this seedling for its compact growth habit and heavy bloom May - June. Of course, the fragrance is lovely and in autumn the foliage turns gorgeous shades of burgundy. The small size makes it perfect for smaller gardens and foundation plantings. A versatile shrub for sun or shade. Thrives in moist soil but somewhat drought tolerant too. Deer resistant.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/love-child-sweetspire/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/IteaLoveChild-015-11842-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>864</ID>
		<Title>Coral Magic Crapemyrtle</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Coral Magic forms a beautiful rounded, dense shrub, loaded with salmon-pink flowers in early summer. The new foliage is a glossy reddish color, eventually becoming dark green throughout the summer. Coral is the earliest in the Magic series to bloom and is a heavy rebloomer if stage pruned. Bred by Plant Introductions Inc.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/coral-magic-crapemyrtle/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/LagerstFirstEditionsCoralMagic-08-9690-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>875</ID>
		<Title>Lunar Magic® Crapemyrtle</Title>
		<baileyDescription>This beautiful crape combines rich purple-black foliage, loads of solid white flower clusters on red stems and a beautiful upright oval shape. Compared to Moonlight Magic™, Lunar Magic® is much more generous in flower production and more intermediate in stature. This prolific bloomer starts flowering in June and can be cycle pruned to bring plants into flower every 35-45 days for sales from early summer through fall. The 2017 growing season was a real test for Cercospora and powdery mildew with many varieties succumbing to the unusually high disease pressure, but Lunar Magic® came through unscathed.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/lunar-magic-crapemyrtle/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/LagLunarMagic-007-13299-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>903</ID>
		<Title>Plum Magic Crapemyrtle</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Plum Magic forms a dense shrub covered in fuchsia-pink blooms by July. The foliage on this rounded shrub emerges plum-purple in color and eventually matures to rich dark green, setting off the bright flowers. Plum blooms just before Purple and is a heavy rebloomer if stage pruned. Bred by Plant Introductions Inc.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/plum-magic-crapemyrtle/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/LagerstFirstEditionsPlumMagic-072-9696.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>913</ID>
		<Title>Purple Magic Crapemyrtle</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Purple Magic is our best-selling green leaf variety. Dark purple flowers cover the rounded, dense shrub from base to tip. Glossy green leaves remain disease free all season. This blooming machine flowers a few days later than Plum and is a heavy rebloomer if staged pruned. Bred by Plant Introductions Inc..</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/purple-magic-crapemyrtle/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/LagerstFirstEditionsPurpleMagic-36-10205-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>922</ID>
		<Title>Red Magic™ Crapemyrtle</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[An early summer bloomer with brilliant red flowers that form a dense, compact shrub only 6-10' tall. The foliage emerges with a red tint and transforms to a deep green in the summer, setting off the true red flowers. Blooms in summer on new wood, prune in late winter. Exhibits outstanding resistance to leaf spot and powdery mildew. Bred by Plant Introductions Inc.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/red-magic-crapemyrtle/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/LagerstFirstEditionsRedMagicPPAF-00-10210-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>932</ID>
		<Title>Ruffled Red Magic™ Crapemyrtle</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Talk about red AND ruffled! This new crapemyrtle has distinctly different, carnation-like, glowing red flowers that show beautifully against the lustrous dark green foliage. Foliage turns orange-red in fall. The habit is upright, but compact, with dense branching, making a nice small tree form. It is also highly resistant to Cercospora leaf spot and powdery mildew, which is quite a breeding accomplishment in red crapes. Bred by Plant Introductions, Inc.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/ruffled-red-magic-crapemyrtle/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/FE_RuffledRed_Blog.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>940</ID>
		<Title>Sunset Magic™ Crapemyrtle</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Talk about a sizzling combination! This compact beauty has large red inflorescences that cover the plant when they bloom. Sunset Magic™ flowers more heavily than other reds with dark foliage. Deep black-purple leaves are flat, lustrous and hold their dark color into late summer. Foliage has been disease-free to date. Bred by Plant Introductions, Inc.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/sunset-magic-crapemyrtle/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/LagerstFirstEditionsSunsetMagic-07-12433-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>948</ID>
		<Title>Twilight Magic™ Crapemyrtle</Title>
		<baileyDescription>The combination of deep plum-colored foliage and pink flowers is stunning. This large shrub/small tree really stands out in the landscape when it blooms. Flower production is profuse compared to Delta Jazz™ and its disease resistance is excellent. Even when not in flower, the dark foliage is handsome all on its own. Very good mildew resistance. An excellent alternative to purple leaf plums in areas where plums are defoliated by August. Bred by Plant Introductions, Inc.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/twilight-magic-crapemyrtle/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/LagerstFirstEditionsTwilightMagic-05-12001-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>955</ID>
		<Title>Straight Talk® Privet</Title>
		<baileyDescription>A natural substitute for ‘Sky Pencil’ holly in colder climates, Straight Talk® is narrow and upright. It can be used as vertical accent or grouped for hedging. In addition to being cold hardy and drought-tolerant, it’s easy to grow in a wide range of soils and tolerates urban conditions. Minimal seed production after five years in Minnesota trials. Deciduous. Found by Mike Jeronimus of Green Acres Nursery in Golden, Colorado. ®CA</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/straight-talk-privet/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/LigStraightTalk022-10118.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>963</ID>
		<Title>Snow White™ Mockorange</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[A repeat flowering hybrid, Snow White™ boasts 2" double flowers borne in clusters that bloom abundantly in spring and then again in summer. A versatile shrub with pure white, deliciously fragrant flowers. Introduced by Plants Nouveau.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/snow-white-mockorange/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/PhilFirstEditionsSnowWhite-02-6354-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>970</ID>
		<Title>Amber Jubilee™ Ninebark</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Amber Jubilee™ was selected for its striking new foliage in glowing tones of orange, yellow and gold. Rounded and dense in habit, this shrub with its bold array of colors makes an eye-catching hedge. Delicate white blooms are produced in spring. Summer foliage is green. Can be stage pruned in production through July to force colorful new growth. Fall foliage is highlighted with tones of red and purple, making this mildew resistant ninebark appealing over the entire season. Plant in full sun for best performance. Result of a controlled cross between 'Darts Gold' and Diablo® ninebark. Selected at Jeffries Nursery in Manitoba, Canada. (CPBR #4765, ®CA)]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/amber-jubilee-ninebark/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/PhysoopFirstEditionsAmberJubilee-163-7448-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>2,3,4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>988</ID>
		<Title>Fireside® Ninebark</Title>
		<baileyDescription>We selected this new ninebark because of the stunning foliage. Reddish new growth matures to deep red-purple foliage that holds its color reliably all summer, which we have witnessed in our trials in Georgia and other test sites. Add to that, Fireside™ doesn’t show any signs of powdery mildew in the field or in production. The leaf size is intermediate; bigger than Little Devil™ but smaller than Diabolo®. Pinkish-white flowers bloom in spring and foliage turns deep purple in fall. The plant habit is tidier than other Physocarpus with a rounded, upright shape.
</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/fireside-ninebark/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/PhysoFireside-07-7453-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>3,4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>998</ID>
		<Title>Little Devil™ Ninebark</Title>
		<baileyDescription>This improved ninebark has an upright spreading habit and fine textured, dark foliage that sets it apart from other ninebark. It is also mildew-resistant and low maintenance as it needs little to no pruning and is free from pest and disease issues and adapts to wet or dry soil. Clusters of small purplish-white flowers in June contrast nicely with the burgundy foliage. Little Devil is a good substitute for barberry in areas of the country where barberry may be invasive. Bred by David Zlesak.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/little-devil-ninebark/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/PhysooFirstEditionsLittleDevil-04-5334-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>3,4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1198</ID>
		<Title>Crème Brûlée™ Potentilla</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Add a pop of white to the landscape with this double flowering potentilla. Bright white flowers adorn this rounded shrub throughout the entire summer. Dark green foliage contrasts beautifully with the flowers. Introduced by Bailey Nurseries, Inc.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/creme-brulee-potentilla/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/PotentillafrFirstEditionsCremeBrule-07-9558-1-1.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>2,3,4,5,6</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1210</ID>
		<Title>Lemon Meringue™ Potentilla</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Lemon Meringue™ is loaded with light yellow double flowers that might remind you of a rose. Blooms all summer on a tidy little plant that forms a round, compact shrub with little pruning required. Deer resistant. Introduced by Bailey Nurseries, Inc.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/lemon-meringue-potentilla/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/PotentillafrFirstEditionsLemonMeringue-04-9594-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>2,3,4,5,6</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1221</ID>
		<Title>Mandarin Tango® Potentilla</Title>
		<baileyDescription>The 1” single round flowers are a lovely shade of orange with just a hint of red in them that comes from the parent ‘Red Robin’.  Beautifully compact, it forms a rounded shrub reaching only 2-3’ in height and spread, making it perfect for the foundation. How many shrubs do we have that bloom all summer like Potentilla? Deer resistant. Bred by Jeffries Nurseries (CPBRAF)</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/mandarin-tango-potentilla/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/PotentillaMandarianTango-07-12869-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>2,3,4,5,6</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1226</ID>
		<Title>Marmalade® Potentilla</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Bred by Dr. Wilbert Ronald at Jeffries Nursery near Winnipeg, Canada, you can be assured this potentilla is going to handle all that winter can throw at it. An intense shade of orange, this double flowered form adds to the 1-2-3 punch of our other potentilla cultivars in First Editions®. Very tight habit with dark green foliage, it blooms from early summer through fall and handles tough conditions. Deer resistant.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/marmalade-potentilla/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/PotentillaMarmalade-006-12870-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>2,3,4,5,6</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1228</ID>
		<Title>Electric Lights™ Double Pink Azalea</Title>
		<baileyDescription>From the deciduous azalea breeding program at the University of Minnesota, this is the first double-flowered form and it is a beauty! In spring, double pink, fragrant flowers smother the plant in color. Soft green foliage turns a good burgundy in the fall. Plants form an upright mound in the landscape and tolerate full sun to part shade. Flower buds are hardy to -30*F. Introduced by Bailey Nurseries, Inc.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/electric-lights-double-pink-azalea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/RhodFirstEditonsElectricLightsDoublePink-02-11466-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1236</ID>
		<Title>Tiger Eyes® Cutleaf Staghorn Sumac</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Tiger Eyes® is a beautiful golden-leafed form of cutleaf staghorn sumac. New growth is a lively chartreuse green, quickly changing to yellow, both colors contrasting nicely with the rosy-pink leaf stems. The branches angle upward while the deeply cut leaflets drape downward. As magnificent as the summer colors are, the dramatic effect of yellow, orange and intense scarlet in autumn are unparalleled. Tolerates a wide range of soils as well as urban conditions, and is adaptable to both poorly drained soils and very dry soil. Doesn't sucker profusely and does not have heavy seed set. Discovered by Steve Jorgensen of Bailey Nurseries. 2007 Gold Medal Plant Award winner. (C®)]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/tiger-eyes-cutleaf-staghorn-sumac/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Tiger-Eyes-e1709928838904.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1247</ID>
		<Title>Iceberg Alley® Sageleaf Willow</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Iceberg Alley™, a native plant discovered by the Memorial University of Newfoundland and Labrador Botanical Garden. Powdery, silver foliage of this small shrub is a great addition to the landscape, adding texture and contrast when combined with other shrubs. Forming a rounded shrub and does not overtake the landscape, reaching a height and spread of about 5' (a bit shorter in very cold areas and a bit taller in warmer zones). It blooms in spring with silver catkins, red stamens and nectar for pollinators.  Tolerant of moist soils and a good choice for rain gardens. Grows best in full sun and tolerates pruning beautifully. Consider cutting the stems in early spring for the decorative catkins.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/iceberg-alley-sageleaf-willow/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/SalixIcebergAlley-002-13138-01-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>2,3,4,5,6</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1255</ID>
		<Title>Matcha Ball® Ash Leaf Spirea</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Matcha Ball® forms a perfect round ball of pretty fern-like foliage in a fresh shade of green. (That green color reminded us of Matcha tea, thus the name.) When the foliage first emerges in very early spring there is a hint of color in the leaves and petioles that ranges from red to orange-peach in color, ultimately maturing to green. Unlike Sem, Matcha Ball®  sparsely blooms and doesn’t develop suckers so it maintains a tight round form throughout the growing season. Fall color is yellow. Prefers moist, well-drained organic soil. Tolerates full sun to some light shade. Discovered by Denis Levac of Québec, Canada.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/matcha-ball-ash-leaf-spirea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/SorbariaMatchaBall-096-11813-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>3,4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1261</ID>
		<Title>Pink Sparkler™ Birchleaf Spirea</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[If you are a fan of Spirea 'Tor', you will love this new twist on Spiraea betulifolia. Bred in France, Pink Sparkler™ blooms in early summer with large pink flowers at the terminals of this rounded shrub. An added bonus is in the autumn, when new flowers are formed and bloom along the leaf axils in each stem. These flowers are smaller, but there are more of them and add a pop of pink color to the fall landscape. Then, the leaves turn a lovely burgundy-red in autumn. The shape is a lovely rounded mound and this plant needs very little pruning to keep its perfect shape. (CPBR 6042)]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/pink-sparkler-birchleaf-spirea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/SpiraeabetFirstEditionsPinkSparkler-03-11364-1.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>3,4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1270</ID>
		<Title>Sundrop™ Spirea</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[A natural hybrid of 'Goldmound' and 'Daphne', Sundrop™ was discovered by Terry Schwartz of Bailey Nurseries, Inc. Beautiful sprays of pink flowers in early summer stand out against petite, golden foliage. This natural dwarf with a rounded habit requires little or no pruning. Our trials show Sundrop™ to be hardier than most golden spirea. Foliage holds its golden-yellow color even in the summer heat.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/sundrop-spirea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/SpiraeaFirstEditionsSundrop-04-2588-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>3,4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1279</ID>
		<Title>Little Spark®  Spirea</Title>
		<baileyDescription>With all the problems with Spirea ‘Goldflame’ reverting, Little Spark® will be the perfect substitution with an even more compact habit. This little spirea has orange new growth and holds its yellow foliage color throughout the summer, even in full sun situations. A summer bloomer, the pink flowers arise just above the foliage, and if you give them a quick shear when they are done, it will bloom again in late summer. Fall color includes shades of pink, creating a multi-toned effect. Bred by Minier.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/little-spark-spirea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/SpireaLittleSpark-021-12640-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>3,4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1280</ID>
		<Title>Superstar™ Spirea</Title>
		<baileyDescription>This superstar is a branch sport of ‘Froebelii’, with a smaller more compact form. Foliage is deep green, showing off the stunning, scarlet red new growth to its best advantage. Pink blossoms grace the plant in June, and it will rebloom in August if spent flowers are pruned. The three-season appeal continues with an excellent bronze fall color. Discovered by Denis Levac of Quebec, Canada and introduced by Bailey Nurseries.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/superstar-spirea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/SpiraeaxFirstEditionsSuperstar-66-5943-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>3,4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1291</ID>
		<Title>Firegold® Spirea</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Firegold® stands out because of its brilliant lemon-lime foliage. New growth is soft yellow changing to lemon, and finally to lime-green. White flowers, typical of the species, appear in spring along gracefully arching branches. The color is stable and at its most brilliant in full sun. This plant came to us from Denis Levac of Québec, Canada. (CPBR #2754)</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/firegold-spirea/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/SpiraeaxvanFirstEditionsFiregold-07-5279-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1307</ID>
		<Title>Candy™ Coralberry</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Plump, candy-pink berries ripen in early fall, as the last of summer's small pink flowers swell into pearls. As the leaves fall, each arching stem is adorned with berries which remain on through the winter. Compact form for the border or in masse. Do not ingest berries. Bred by Peter Kolster.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/candy-coralberry/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/SymphxdoorFirstEditionsCandy-04-7667-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1315</ID>
		<Title>Galaxy™ Snowberry</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Plump, bridal-white berries ripen in early fall, adding interest to the autumn and winter garden on a neat, compact plant. Bred by Peter Kolster.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/galaxy-snowberry/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/SymphxdoorFirstEditionsGalaxy-05-8882-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1323</ID>
		<Title>Virtual Violet® Lilac</Title>
		<baileyDescription>With shiny violet new leaves, deep purple stems, raspberry-purple buds and fragrant violet flowers, Virtual Violet® is aptly named. Leaf petioles remain violet well into the summer. The habit is upright instead of rounded and compact. The dense habit makes it a great choice for a hedge in smaller spaces as well as a welcome addition to foundation plantings. Remarkably mildew-free. This is a controlled cross between Charles Joly and two outstanding National Arboretum varieties. Bred by Don Selinger, Bailey Nurseries retiree. (CBRAF)</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/virtual-violet-lilac/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/SyrVirtualViolet-09-5325-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>3,4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1331</ID>
		<Title>Little Lady™ Lilac</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Imagine the beautifully fragrant flowers of 'Miss Kim' lilac on a more compact, restrained plant. That is exactly what you have with Little Lady™. In late spring, the dark pink buds open to lilac pink, with a heady fragrance that will tickle your nose! The foliage is similar to 'Miss Kim' and is a nice fresh green. The mature size makes this plant perfect for foundation plantings, but it can also be used en masse, or as an informal hedge where you don't need a lot of height. At maturity, it is about half the size of 'Miss Kim'. Rock solid hardy, it was bred on the northern plains of North America and will thrive even in zone 2. Developed by our friends at Jeffries Nursery in Canada.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/little-lady-lilac/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/SyrLittleLady-041-12871-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>2,3,4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1332</ID>
		<Title>Opening Day™ Doublefile Viburnum</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[With perfectly round, baseball-size flowers in April, we couldn't resist calling this beacon of spring Opening Day™. Compact plants are covered with, snowball-like flowers that open with a tinge of green and quickly mature to pure white. Plants are tight in habit with dark green foliage that turns beautiful shades of cabernet in the fall. The deeply corrugated foliage is spring green and flawless through the growing season. Easy and fast to produce, this should be a production staple. Bred by Plant Introductions, Inc. (CPBRAF)]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/opening-day-doublefile-viburnum/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/ViburnumFirstEditionsOpeningDay-05-12168-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1343</ID>
		<Title>Blue Puffball™ Chastetree</Title>
		<baileyDescription>A true genetic dwarf, Blue Puffball™ is even more compact than Delta Blues™. It forms a perfect ball-shaped plant with short internodes and thick foliage. Mid-green foliage is clean into fall with minimal leaf spot. Deep blue, fragrant flowers bloom from June to September. Flowers form on new growth like Buddleia so it can be used as a dieback shrub in colder areas. Bred by Plant Introductions, Inc. (CPBRAF)</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/blue-puffball-chastetree/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/VitexFirstEditionsBluePuffball-01-11840-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>6,7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1354</ID>
		<Title>Delta Blues™ Chastetree</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Delta Blues™ is the first intermediate Vitex in the market. It is not nearly as coarse as other Vitex with a compact, rounded to upright growth habit. It has fragrant, dark bluish-purple flowers. The foliage is dark green, fragrant and more refined than other selections. Delta Blues adapts to acid or alkaline soils as long as the site is well-drained. It is also salt-tolerant. Introduced by Plant Introductions Inc.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/delta-blues-chastetree/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/VitexFirstEditionsDeltaBlues-01-11636-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>6,7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1365</ID>
		<Title>Flip Side® Chastetree</Title>
		<baileyDescription>This beauty is a seedling selection from Vitex trifolia ‘Purpurea’ x V. agnus-castus that combines the best of both parents. Flip Side® is cloaked in 8-inch panicles of fragrant, deep purple flowers that attract a nonstop parade of pollinators. It’s also a strong rebloomer. Flip Side® got its name because the greyish olive-green leaves are dusky purple on the lower surface. While V. trifolia ‘Purpurea’ is only hardy to Zone 9, Flip Side® has been hardy in Athens, Georgia for a number of years, surviving a zone 7 winter. Flip Side® is much more compact than either parent. This is a very cool plant for warmer regions.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/flip-side-chastetree/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/VitexFlipSide-01-12829-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1375</ID>
		<Title>Galactic Pink® Chastetree</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Galactic Pink® has flowers that are a beautiful shade of pink and intermediate in size. The fragrant flowers, born in long panicles, bloom from June to October and attract pollinators by the dozens. The dark green foliage is clean and the branching is dense and full. Maturing at a slightly smaller size than Delta Blues™. Like all Vitex, it prefers well drained soils, is salt tolerant, and deer resistant.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/galactic-pink-chastetree/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/VitexGalaticPink-003-13360-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>6,7,8,9</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1376</ID>
		<Title>Rainbow Sensation™ Weigela</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Even before the first flowers appear, Rainbow Sensation™ stands out due to the attractive, variegated foliage. Dense clusters of soft pink flowers bloom profusely in May or June. Rainbow Sensation™ is especially well suited to urban environments where it is exceptionally cold hardy and performs beautifully with minimal care. Introduced by Plants Nouveau.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/rainbow-sensation-weigela/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/WeigelaFirstEditionsRainbowSensation-07-7669.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1387</ID>
		<Title>Shining Sensation™ Weigela</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Shining Sensation™ is a blooming machine with pink funnel-shaped flowers that bloom in May and June, and then sporadically through summer. Shiny, burgundy foliage appears as though it has been polished, and contrasts nicely with the pink flowers making this selection a cut above the rest. Long, arching stems provide a handsome architectural element to the mixed border. A Plants Nouveau Introduction.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/shining-sensation-weigela/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/WeigelaflFirstEditionsShiningSensation-02-6368-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1406</ID>
		<Title>Autumn Revolution™ Bittersweet</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[A revolutionary breakthrough in bittersweet culture. Imagine never having to wonder if you're buying or selling a male or female plant again. The majority of the flowers formed on Autumn Revolution™ are perfect, meaning that the flower itself has both male and female parts. In other words, you only need one plant to bear fruit. Perhaps because of this unique characteristic the fruit production is absolutely extraordinary and the berry size is twice that of the species, but it is not invasive like the Asian species. Truly an improvement for this beloved native vine. Discovered and introduced by Bailey Nurseries, Inc.]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/autumn-revolution-bittersweet/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/CelFirstEditionsAutumnRevolution-101-0895-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>2,3,4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1423</ID>
		<Title>Summer Cascade™ Wisteria</Title>
		<baileyDescription>Blooming in June on new growth, individual flowers are borne on long showy racemes and open as a lovely shade of dark lavender before fading.  Summer Cascade™ is a beautiful flowering vine which can easily cover an arbor or pergola, creating a cool, shady place.  Producing an interesting seed pod in late summer, this vine has lovely multi-season interests and is more reliably cold hardy than other wisteria. Discovered by Betty Matthews in White Bear Lake, Minnesota and given to the University of Minnesota, introduced in partnership with Bailey Nurseries, Inc.</baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/summer-cascade-wisteria/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/WisteriamacFirstEditionsSummerCascade-03-5653-1-1-scaled.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>4,5,6,7,8</Zones>
	</post>
	<post>
		<ID>1441</ID>
		<Title>Technito® Arborvitae</Title>
		<baileyDescription><![CDATA[Technito® has the attractive dark green color of 'Techny' and retains the winter foliage color just as well. This cultivar, being noticeably denser, is an improvement because it requires less shearing to retain a compact pyramidal outline. Discovered by Johnson’s Nursery, Inc. of Wisconsin and co- introduced by Bailey Nurseries, Inc. (C®)]]></baileyDescription>
		<Permalink>https://firsteditionsplants.com/product/technito-arborvitae/</Permalink>
		<ImageFeatured>https://firsteditionsplants.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/ThujaoccTechnitoArborvitae-14-2229.jpg</ImageFeatured>
		<Zones>3,4,5,6,7</Zones>
	</post>
</data>
